MacKaye Family papers ML-5
Rauner Special Collections Library
- Benton MacKaye, 1880-1976; 21
  - Box: 190, 1910- 1950's (Box 190)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Notecards: Who's Who - List of Friends and Aquaintances, undated (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Notecards: Pack M - Notes about Daily Routine in 1929 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Notecards: Books, 1943-1949 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Notecards: Camping Lists, undated (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - Notecards: Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - Notecards: Inventory, 1945 (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - Notecards: Special, 1949 (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - Notecards: Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - Notecards: Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 190, Folder 25)
    - Notecards: Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 190, Folder 26)
    - Notecards: Accounts, 1957-1959 (Box 190, Folder 27)
    - Notecards: Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 190, Folder 28)
    - Notecards: Index of Articles by Benton MacKaye, undated (Box 190, Folder 29)
    - Notecards: "The Blizzards Men of 88", "Chaplin Hill," "Dartmouth Flood Plains", undated (Box 190, Folder 30)
    - Notecards: "International Law" and Miscellaneous, undated (Box 190, Folder 31)
    - Notecards: MacKaye Family Persons and their Works, undated (Box 190, Folder 32)
    - Notecards: Quotations, REA, undated (Box 190, Folder 33)
    - Notecards: Students, Talks re. Appalachian Trail, 1939 (Box 190, Folder 34)
    - Notecards: Wilderness Society, 1947 (Box 190, Folder 35)
    - Notecards: Locations of Possessions, undated (Box 190, Folder 36)
    - Christmas Cards, 1936 (Box 190, Folder 37)
    - Postcards: Benton Mackay and Betty's, 1910-1930 (Box 190, Folder 38)
  - Contains Postcards and Greeting Cards, 1930's-1970's (Box 191)
    Contains Postcards and Greeting Cards
  - Box: 192, 1880's -1960's (Box 192)
    Box: 192
    - Miscellaneous: Address Books, undated (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous: Address Books, undated (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Miscelleneous: AT Walkers, 1950-1951 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous: John Michael Barnes Graduation, 1965 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneosu: Benton MacKaye Book List, 1979 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous: Book of Daily Biblical Verses, undated (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton MacKaye Boyhood Sketches, 1880's-1890's (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneosu: Benton MacKaye Boyhood Writings, 1893 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous: Re.Harvey and Anne Broome's Wedding, 1937 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous: Harvey Broome's Comment on Benton MacKaye, 1934 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton MacKaye Calling Cards, undated (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous: Chart of Benton MacKaye's Diet, 1921 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous: Children's Book of Wild Animals 1886 (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton MacKaye's Chores, 1908 (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous: Contents of Letter Boxes from Shirley House and Cottage, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton's Dances, 1890's (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous: Department of Labor Honor and ID Cards, 1918-1919 (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous: Description of Harry and Lucy Johnsons's Shirley Property, undated (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous: Paragon Drawing Book with Drawings by Benton MacKaye, 1887 (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous: Family Tree, undated (Box 192, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous: Fifty Year Anniversary of Benton MacKaye's Arrival in Shirley, 1937 (Box 192, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous: Harvard Class of 1900 Form Letters and Other Material, 1960's (Box 192, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous: 50th Harvard Reunion, 1950 (Box 192, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous: Hazel's Census List, 1938 (Box 192, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous: Instructions For Making Forest Surveys and Maps, 1907 (Box 192, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous: List for "Living Wilderness", undated (Box 192, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous: List of "Who's Who in the Cosmos Club", 1958 (Box 192, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous: Mrs. Steele Makaye's Final Illness and Death, 1924 (Box 192, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous: Membership Cards and Certificates, 1950's (Box 192, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous: Knoxville Parties, 1935-1936 (Box 192, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous: Memorabilia, 1910-1920's (Box 192, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous: Note and Ribbon from Benton MacKaye's Baby Nurse, undated (Box 192, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous: Notebooks, cor1907-1908 (Box 192, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton MacKaye's "Pantheistic Grace", 1963 (Box 192, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous: Peaver Family Tree, 1947 (Box 192, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous: Philosopher's Club Material, 1936 (Box 192, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous: Poem " Yes, Benton Loves A Brakerman" by Percy MacKaye, 1891 (Box 192, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous: Notice on Benton's 83rd Birthday, 1962 (Box 192, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous: School Notebooks and Papers, 1890 (Box 192, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous: Socialist Party Membership Card, undated (Box 192, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous: Signs for Marking Trails - Bridgeman School Hikes, undated (Box 192, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton MacKaye Solstice Cards, 1937-1940 (Box 192, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous: Song Sheet "Benton MacKaye", undated (Box 192, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous: The Squannacook River Plan, 1931 (Box 192, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous: Tables of Data on Forests, 1907 (Box 192, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous: Thanksgiving Dinner Shirley Hermitage, 1922 (Box 192, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous: Tributes and Obituaries for Benton MacKaye, 1970's (Box 192, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous: Benton Mackay's Pocketcopie of the US Constitution, undated (Box 192, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous: Who's Who Connecticut River Valley, undated (Box 192, Folder 49)
  - Contains Bank Statements and Cancelled Checks, 1910-1970's (Box 193)
    Contains Bank Statements and Cancelled Checks
  - Box: 194, 1918-1970's (Box 194)
    Box: 194
    - Business Papers: Book of Expenses, 1903 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Business Papers: Cashbooks, 1921-1922 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Business Papers: Living Expenses, 1921-1922 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Business Papers: Accounts, 1930 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Business Papers: Expenses, 1959-1962 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Business Papers: Expenses, 1969 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Business Papers: Birth Cerificate Papers Benton MacKaye, 1924 (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Business Papers: Chicago Eye, Ear, Nose and Throat College Stock Information, 1936 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Business Papers: Civil Service Commission, 1941 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Business Papers: Cosmos Club Personnel, 1960 (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Business Papers: Cost of Living, Shirley Center, 1948 (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Business Papers: US Department of Agriculture, 1940 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Business Papers: US Department of Labor Appointments, 1918-1920 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Business Papers: Group Health Association, 1940 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Business Papers: Income Taxes, 1940's (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Business Papers: Income Taxes, 1940's (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Business Papers: Income Taxes, 1930's-1940's (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - Business Papers: Income Taxes, 1940's-1950's (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - Business Papers: Income Taxes, 1960's-1970's (Box 194, Folder 19)
    - Business Papers: Literary Executors, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 20)
    - Business Papers: Medicare, 1970's (Box 194, Folder 21)
    - Business Papers: NARCE, 1970's (Box 194, Folder 22)
    - Business Papers: Painting and Repair on Shirley Cottage, 1961 (Box 194, Folder 23)
    - Business Papers: Federal Retirement, 1940's (Box 194, Folder 24)
    - Business Papers: Royalities Statements, 1930's-1960's (Box 194, Folder 25)
    - Business Papers: Selective Service, 1940's (Box 194, Folder 26)
    - Business Papers: Social Security, 1971 (Box 194, Folder 27)
    - Business Papers: Statement of the Smokey Mountain Hiking Club Dance and Music Program, 1935 (Box 194, Folder 28)
    - Business Papers: Summons served on Benton MacKaye, 1892 (Box 194, Folder 29)
    - Business Papers: Wilderness Expenses, 1946 (Box 194, Folder 30)
    - Business Papers: Last Will and Testament, 1925 (Box 194, Folder 31)
    - Business Papers: List of Dartmouth Papers, 1972 (Box 194, Folder 32)
    - Business Papers: List of Doctors, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 33)
    - Business Papers: List of "Ben's Folks", 1959 (Box 194, Folder 34)
    - Business Papers: List about Wills, 1956 (Box 194, Folder 35)
    - Business Papers: Lists of Contents of Suitcases, 1940's-1950's (Box 194, Folder 36)
    - Business Papers: Miscellaneous Bills and Receipts, 1920's-1950's (Box 194, Folder 37)
    - Business Papers: Receipts and Bills Knoxville, 1933-1936 (Box 194, Folder 38)
    - Business Papers: Receipts and Bills, Massachusetts, 1936 (Box 194, Folder 39)
    - Business Papers: Miscellaneous Receipts and Bills, 1971-1974 (Box 194, Folder 40)
    - Business Papers: News Clippings, 1942 (Box 194, Folder 41)
    - Business Papers: Memo by Mrs. Robert Hall Laing re. MacKaye Family Tree, undated (Box 194, Folder 42)
    - Business Papers: Sale of Cottage, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 43)
    - Business Papers: Cottage, 1920's (Box 194, Folder 44)
    - Business Papers: Grove House and Inheritance, Hazel MacKaye's Death, 1944-1945 (Box 194, Folder 45)
    - Business Papers: Grove House Deeds, 1920 (Box 194, Folder 46)
    - Business Papers: Deed to Grove House and Agreement on Storage, 1960 (Box 194, Folder 47)
    - Business Papers: Statement of Expenses: Grove House and Cottage, 1926 (Box 194, Folder 48)
    - Business Papers: Recipt and Bills for Grove House and Cottage, 1920's-1930's (Box 194, Folder 49)
    - Business Papers: Tax Receipts and Other Documents for Grove House and Cottage, 1938-1964 (Box 194, Folder 50)
    - Business Papers: Grove House Rental, 1942 (Box 194, Folder 51)
    - Business Papers: Hazel's Business Matters, 1930's (Box 194, Folder 52)
    - Business Papers: Hazel MacKaye's Illness, Death and Will, 1938-1944 (Box 194, Folder 53)
    - Business Papers: Hazel MacKaye's Illness, Death and Will, 1938-1944 (Box 194, Folder 54)
    - Business Papers: MacKaye Family Association, 1927-1928 (Box 194, Folder 55)
    - Business Papers: MacKaye Family Association, 1920 (Box 194, Folder 56)
    - Business Papers: MacKaye Family Association, 1923-1927 (Box 194, Folder 57)
    - Business Papers: MacKaye Family Association, 1920-1966 (Box 194, Folder 58)
    - Business Papers: Shirley Property Upkeep, 1930's (Box 194, Folder 59)
    - Business Papers: Informationm on the MacKaye Family Plot in Woodlawn Cemetary, NY, 1939 (Box 194, Folder 60)
  - Box: 195, 1920's-1970 (Box 195)
    Box: 195
    - Letters to Newspapers, 1931 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Letters to Newspapers, 1944-1949 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Letters to Newspapers, 1950-1959 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Letters to Newspapers, 1960-1969 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Letters to Newspapers, 19471-1972 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Letters to Newspapers, undated (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1900-1919 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1922-1927 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1928-1929 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1930-1933 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1934-1939 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1940-1949 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1951-1959 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1960-1967 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1968-1969 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, undated (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Appalachian Trail, 1920's (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper Clippings: 1954 Conservation Award (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings: VSDI Award, 1966 (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - "Journal of the American Institute of Planners", 1975 (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Shirley Bi-Centennial, 1953 (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - Journal Clipping: "Long, Long Trail Awinding" in "American Forests", 1971 (Box 195, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clipping About Benton MacKaye, 1970-1975 (Box 195, Folder 23)
    - Journal Clipping: "Through Wilderness And Real Estate: The Applachian Trail" in "Environmental Journal, 1972 (Box 195, Folder 24)
    - Writing: "Benton MacKaye - The Appalachian Trail, A Lighnting Rod Of Civilization" by John R. Ross, undated (Box 195, Folder 25)
    - AIA Journals with articles on Benton MacKaye, 1971 (Box 195, Folder 26)
    - Journal Clipping: "Benton MacKaye - The Verdant" in "American Forests", 1964 (Box 195, Folder 27)
    - Writing: John Ross's Proposal for a Benton MacKaye Biography, undated (Box 195, Folder 28)
    - Journal Clippings: Re. Forest Service's 50th Anniversary Honor, 1955 (Box 195, Folder 29)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Harvey Broome's Obituaries, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Howard Zahniser Obituaries, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Obituaries, 1930's-1960's (Box 195, Folder 32)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Obituaries, 1930's-1950's (Box 195, Folder 33)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Theodore Roosevelt Island Memorial, 1960 (Box 195, Folder 34)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Shirley Center Film, 1938 (Box 195, Folder 35)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Charles Darwin, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Abraham Lincoln, 1959 (Box 195, Folder 37)
    - Newspaper Clippings: Decapitation, 1952 (Box 195, Folder 38)
    - Newspaper Clippings: "Milwaukee Leader" Editorials, 1920 (Box 195, Folder 39)
    - Newspaper Clippings: "Milwaukee Leader" Editorials, 1920 (Box 195, Folder 40)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's-1960's (Box 195, Folder 41)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's-1960's (Box 195, Folder 42)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1950's (Box 195, Folder 43)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1950's (Box 195, Folder 44)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1906, 1950's (Box 195, Folder 45)
  - Box: 196, 1905-1960's (Box 196)
    Box: 196
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1906, 1950's (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1930's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1929-1950's (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1905, 1920's-1950's (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1950's (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1931, 1950's, 1974 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1929-1940 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1941 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1939-1940 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1930's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's-1940's (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's-1950's (Box 196, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1902, 1948, 1950's-1960 (Box 196, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1920's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1929-1958 (Box 196, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1930's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1913, 1920's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's (Box 196, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1930's-1940's (Box 196, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1950's (Box 196, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1930's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1940's-1960's (Box 196, Folder 27)
    - Newspaper Clipping: "The New York Times", 1939 (Box 196, Folder 28)
    - Newspaper Clippings: "Boston Herald", 1939 (Box 196, Folder 29)
    - Newspaper Clippings: "New York Times Book Review", 1939 (Box 196, Folder 30)
    - Newspaper Clippings: "The New York Times", 1939 (Box 196, Folder 31)
    - Applachian Trail Markers, undated (Box 196, Folder 32)
    - Hammer Lantern Plates - Teaching Slides, Book Plates, undated (Box 196, Folder 33)
    - Hammer Lantern Plates, undated (Box 196, Folder 34)
  - Box: 197, 1920's-1970's (Box 197)
    Box: 197
    - Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Clippings, 1920's-1950's (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Clippings, 1920's-1930's (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Applalachian Trail: "Guide To The Applalachian Trail", 1934 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Clippings, 1974 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Clippings, 1930's-1950's (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Appalachian Trail: Miscellaneous Clippings and Ephemera, 1930's-1970's (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1925, 1975 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1948, 1969-1973 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1930's-1950's (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1930's-1970's (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1930's-1970's (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1929, 1970's (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1960's-1970's (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1967's-1973's (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1930 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Appalachian Trail: Trail Conference Materials and Writings, 1931 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Appalachian Trail: ATC Newsletter, 1974 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Appalachian Trail: The Georgia Appalachian Trail Club, 1930's-1960's (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Appalachian Trail: The Georgia Mountains, 1930's, 1960's (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Appalachian Trail: The Natural Bridge Appalachian Trail Club, 1930's (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Appalachian Trail: The New England Trail Conference, 1920's (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Appalachian Trail: The Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, 1960's-1970's (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - Appalachian Trail: The Potomac Appalachian Trail Club, 1928-1973 (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Appalachian Trail: Smokey Mountain Hiking Club, 1930's-1950's (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - Appalachian Trail: US Department of the Interior Publication, 1971 (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - Appalachian Trail: Correspondence, 1922-1964 (Box 197, Folder 26)
    - Appalachian Trail: Legislation HR 2142, 1942-1963 (Box 197, Folder 27)
    - Appalachian Trail: Old Trailbooks, 1920's-1940's (Box 197, Folder 28)
    - Appalachian Trail: List of what to take on a hike, undated (Box 197, Folder 29)
    - Appalachian Trail: Maps, 1920's (Box 197, Folder 30)
    - Appalachian Trail: Some Benton Mackay's Writing, 1921 (Box 197, Folder 31)
    - Wilderness Society: Legislation HR 9070, 1960's (Box 197, Folder 32)
    - Wilderness Society: Correspondence, 1940's-1950's (Box 197, Folder 33)
    - Wilderness Society: Correspondence, 1940's (Box 197, Folder 34)
    - Wilderness Society: Correspondence, 1939-1941 (Box 197, Folder 35)
    - Wilderness Society: Correspondence, 1933's-1946 (Box 197, Folder 36)
    - Wilderness Society: Meeting Minutes, 1939-1964 (Box 197, Folder 37)
    - Wilderness Society: Meeting Minutes, 1967-1970 (Box 197, Folder 38)
    - Wilderness Society: History, 1935-1947 (Box 197, Folder 39)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1938-1946 (Box 197, Folder 40)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1940-1965 (Box 197, Folder 41)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1946-1957 (Box 197, Folder 42)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 197, Folder 43)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1940-1969 (Box 197, Folder 44)
    - Wilderness Society: Miscellaneous, 1937-1973 (Box 197, Folder 45)
    - Wilderness Society: Business, 1968-1969 (Box 197, Folder 46)
    - Wilderness Society: Busienss, 1968-1969 (Box 197, Folder 47)
    - Wilderness Society: "Wilderness Conservation Leader's Background Information Kit", 1967 (Box 197, Folder 48)
  - Contains Photos of Benton MacKaye and Others, 1920's-1970's (Box 198)
    Contains Photos of Benton MacKaye and Others
  - Contains Maps and Charts including Maps of British Columbia, Winooski Valley, VT Topographics an..., 1910-1970's (Box 199)
    Contains Maps and Charts including Maps of British Columbia, Winooski Valley, VT Topographics and Submerged Coastal Lands
  - Box: 200, 1920-1976 (Box 200)
    Box: 200
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: A, 1920-1954 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "American Institute of Architects Journal (AIA"), 1971-1976 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Annuitant", 1948-1950 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Appalachia", 1975 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Appalachia", 1975-1976 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Appalachian Trailway News", 1949-1969 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Appalachian Trailway News", 1970-1973 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Appalachian Trailway News", 1974-1975 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Atlantic Monthly", 1923 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Boston Region", 1964 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Congressional Digest", 1961 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Congressional Record", 1933-1968 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Cosmos Club Bulletin", 1960's (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "cosmos Club Bulletin", 1950's-1970's (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Forest History" and "Forest Notes", 1960's, 1974 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Harvard Forest", 1966-1968 (Box 200, Folder 16)
  - Box: 201, 1900-1974 (Box 201)
    Box: 201
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Harvard Crimpson", 1910-1912 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Harvard Crimson", 1924-1948 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Harvard Crimson", 1950-1971 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "Harvard Alumni Bulleting" and "The Harvard Ilustrated Magazine", 1900-1912 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Crimpson Quindecennial 1900-1910", 1911 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Magazines, Journals, Newsletters, Bulletins: "The Crimpson Quindecennial 1900-1915", 1916 (Box 201, Folder 6)